I'm going to draw out the view hierarchy diagram for options A, B, and C.
我将要画出选项 A B C 的层次结构图了
We'll start with option A.
我们从选项A开始
It contains a LinearLayout as the root view.
它包含一个 LinearLayout 作为根 View
So let me draw that.
让我们来画吧
Then I want to figure out the next layer of the view hierarchy,
这时我想出下一层的 View 层次
which would be the direct children of this LinearLayout.
应该是 LinearLayout 的直属子 View
I'm going to scroll through the XML file to figure out the direct children
让我们滚动 XML 文件来找出 LinearLayout 的
of this LinearLayout.
直属子 View
We have a TextView, a LinearLayout, another TextView, another TextView,
我们有一个 TextView 一个 LinearLayout 另一个 TextView 另一个 TextView
and then a Button.
和一个按钮
So let me draw that in.
让我画出来
Cool, that looks good, but
酷 看起来不错 不过
we actually skipped over a bunch of XML related to this LinearLayout.
事实上忽略很多与这个 LinearLayout 有关的 XML
This nested LinearLayout contains a Button, a TextView, and a Button.
这个嵌套的 LinearLayout 包含了一个 Button 一个 TextView 和一个 Button
Let's draw those in.
让我们画出来
This is the view hierarchy diagram for option A.
这个就是选项A的层次结构图了
At a high level, there is a parent LinearLayout as the root view.
在高层面上 这是一个被视为根 View 的父 LinearLayout
It contains five children views, and one of the children
它包含了五个子 View 和一个子类
actually is a LinearLayout that contains three more views.
事实上是包含另外三个 View 的 LinearLayout
Great, let's move on to option B.
很好 让我们看看选项B
In option B, we have a parent LinearLayout as a root view again.
在选项B 我们有一个父 LinearLayout 作为根 View
Now, we can figure out the direct children of this LinearLayout.
现在 我们能找出 LinearLayout 的直属子 View
We have a TextView, a LinearLayout, another TextView, another TextView,
我们有一个 TextView 一个 LinearLayout 一个 TextView 另一个 TextView
and a Button.
和一个Button
This nested LinearLayout also has more children.
这个嵌套的 LinearLayout 还有更多子 View
We have a Button, a TextView, and another Button.
我们有一个 Button 一个 TextView 和另外的 Button
Hopefully, you're getting the idea of how to read an XML file
我希望 你知道怎样阅读 XML文件
by looking at the outermost parent first and then going inwards from there.
通过先了解最外围的父 View 然后从这向内继续了解
And last but not least, we have option C.
最后 我们还有选项C
The root view is a LinearLayout again.
根 View 是一个 LinearLayout
Let's look for its direct children.
让我们看看它的直属子 View
We have a LinearLayout followed by a TextView, a TextView, and a button.
我们有一个 LinearLayout 后面跟着一个 TextView 一个 TextView 和一个 Button
Okay, good, so this is a view hierarchy diagram for option C.
好的 很好 这是选项C的视图层次结构图
This looks a little bit different than the other options, so
这与其他选项的看起来不太一样
let's compare them side by side.
让我们一步步对比看看
Here are all the options side by side.
这是一个个的选项
A and B have very similar view hierarchies whereas option C
A和B的视图层次结构图很像 然而C
has a different view hierarchy.
有不同的视图层次结构
This LinearLayout has only four children as opposed to five children in
这个 LinearLayout 只有四个子 View 与其他例子
the other cases.
截然相反（有五个）
Also, since A and B look very similar, we're going to have to look more closely
同时 尽管 A 和 B 看起来很像 我们想要看起来更紧密
at the XML to determine what the difference is between the two.
所以要从 XML 来确定这两者有哪些区别
In the next quiz, you'll look more closely at the XML for each option.
下一个测验里你会更仔细的研究每一个选项的 XML
Then I'll ask you to decide which option you think
之后我会让你做出选择
best accurately describes the layout that we want to build.
哪个最准确的描述了我们想要的布局